[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What term refers to the study of fermentation?", "correct_answer": "Zymurgy", "incorrect_answers": ["Zonary", "Zigadenus", "Zoolatry"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Also known for her record-breaking trip around the world, what American journalist faked insanity in order to study a mental institution from the inside?", "correct_answer": "Nellie Bly", "incorrect_answers": ["Gertrude Ederle", "Lizzie Borden", "Susan B. Anthony"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The diaphragm regulates the amount of light reaching the microscope objective.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of Titanics sister ship?", "correct_answer": "Olympic", "incorrect_answers": ["Amerika", "Frankfurt", "Mesaba"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What city in the US state of Texas is a home of the largest bat colony in North America during the summer?", "correct_answer": "Austin", "incorrect_answers": ["Morton", "Houston", "Pittsburg"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which programming language is based on Horn clauses?", "correct_answer": "Prolog", "incorrect_answers": ["Erlang", "Lisp", "PL/I"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 2006 movie Babel, which actress plays Richard\u2019s wife Susan?", "correct_answer": "Cate Blanchett", "incorrect_answers": ["Jennifer Lopez", "Claire Danes", "Gwyneth Paltrow"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are the three basic parts of an ants body?", "correct_answer": "Head, mesosoma, metasoma", "incorrect_answers": ["Antennae, abdomen, thoraces", "Head, abdomen, metasoma", "Head, thorax, somatomy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On average, a 4-year-old child asks approximately this number of questions a day.", "correct_answer": "437", "incorrect_answers": ["126", "371", "74"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which was the first country to win two consecutive FIFA World Cups in 1958 and 1962?", "correct_answer": "Brazil", "incorrect_answers": ["Italy", "France", "Argentina"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What movie is famous for its depiction of the Omaha beachhead assault of 1944 in its opening 24 minutes?", "correct_answer": "Saving Private Ryan", "incorrect_answers": ["The Thin Red Line", "Letters from Iwo Jima", "Full Metal Jacket"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what state does the classic movie The Color Purple take place?", "correct_answer": "Georgia", "incorrect_answers": ["Louisiana", "Alabama", "South Carolina"]}]